[
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Italy?",
        "answer": "Rome"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Machu Picchu?",
        "answer": "Peru"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mount Etna is located on which island?",
        "answer": "Sicily"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which ocean is the area known as Polynesia located?",
        "answer": "Pacific"
    },
    {
        "question": "William Mynors is the captain that discovered and named what island in 1643?",
        "answer": "Christmas Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "To which group of islands does Corfu belong?",
        "answer": "Ionian islands"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which country is the Great Sandy Desert located?",
        "answer": "Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city is the Prado art gallery located?",
        "answer": "Madrid"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European country replaced the Schilling with the Euro?",
        "answer": "Austria"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European country replaced the Markka with the Euro?",
        "answer": "Finland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European country replaced the Guilder with the Euro?",
        "answer": "The Netherlands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European country replaced the Lev with the Euro?",
        "answer": "Bulgaria"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Hungary`s capital?",
        "answer": "Budapest"
    },
    {
        "question": "The resort city of Aspen is located in which US state?",
        "answer": "Colorado"
    },
    {
        "question": "What military cemetery is located across the Potomac River from the Lincoln Memorial?",
        "answer": "Arlington National Cemetery"
    },
    {
        "question": "Toledo Bend Reservoir is a man-made lake located between what two US states?",
        "answer": "Louisiana and Texas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Latin American country shares its name with a nut?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest country in South America?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which former Soviet Republic in Central Asia has Tashkent as its capital?",
        "answer": "Uzbekistan"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which continent would you find the Atlas Mountains?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Atlas Mountains stretch through which countries?",
        "answer": "Morocco, Algeria and Tunisia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Through which African countries do the Atlas Mountains stretch?",
        "answer": "Morocco, Algeria and Tunisia"
    },
    {
        "question": "During which month is the longest day in the Southern hemisphere?",
        "answer": "December"
    },
    {
        "question": "On what sea is the Crimea?",
        "answer": "The Black Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city was formerly called New Amsterdam?",
        "answer": "New York City"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tenerife is the largest island in which archipelago?",
        "answer": "Canary Islands"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Vanuatu?",
        "answer": "Port Vila"
    },
    {
        "question": "Port Vila is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Vanuatu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Florida?",
        "answer": "Tallahassee"
    },
    {
        "question": "How was the country of Belize known prior to 1973?",
        "answer": "British Honduras"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Irish city`s name is Gaelic for `black pool`?",
        "answer": "Dublin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Mount Olympus?",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "What object marks the ceremonial location of the South Pole?",
        "answer": "A red and white striped pole"
    },
    {
        "question": "What object marks the geographic South Pole?",
        "answer": "A plaque"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city has been awarded the most total Michelin stars as of 2020?",
        "answer": "Tokyo"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Yalu River separates China from which country?",
        "answer": "North Korea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you drive on the Seven Mile Bridge?",
        "answer": "Florida Keys"
    },
    {
        "question": "What U.S. state hosts an underwater music festival?",
        "answer": "Florida"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you take part in the `Battle of the Oranges`?",
        "answer": "Ivrea, Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Equator passes through how many countries?",
        "answer": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. territory markets itself, `Where America`s day begins`?",
        "answer": "Guam -- Located in the North Pacific Ocean, sunrise in Guam occurs 14 hours before it does on America`s east coast."
    },
    {
        "question": "The U.S. Virgin Islands are located in which Ocean?",
        "answer": "Atlantic Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Islands make up the U.S. Virgin Islands?",
        "answer": "The U.S. Virgin Islands consist of Saint Croix, Saint Thomas, Saint John, and Water Island, alongside 50 other tiny islets."
    },
    {
        "question": "What islands make up the British Virgin Islands?",
        "answer": "The British Virgin Islands is a former colony that includes the islands of Virgin Gorda, Tortola, Anegada, and Jost Van Dyke."
    },
    {
        "question": "What U.S. state`s official dessert is Smith Island Cake?",
        "answer": "Smith Island lies about 12 miles off the coast of Maryland in Chesapeake Bay and is home to the its tantalizing state dessert."
    },
    {
        "question": "Norman Rockwell is the official artist of which state?",
        "answer": "Massachusetts -- He spent 25 years living in the Berkshires of Massachusetts."
    },
    {
        "question": "What country shares a border with Cambodia to the northwest?",
        "answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. town is home to the world`s largest rose bush?",
        "answer": "Tombstone, Arizona"
    },
    {
        "question": "NAFTA is a trade agreement between the US and what other two countries?",
        "answer": "Mexico and Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two states share a border with Florida?",
        "answer": "Alabama and Georgia"
    }
]